Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/pacitas-02b6aa67 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care

Acute Care

Leadership

Certifications

Critical Care RN

PALS

ACLS

BLS

Pacita Sangalang

BSN, RN, CCRN, CPN

Los Angeles, California

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Leadership, Mentoring Coaching, Facilitating, Communication, Customer Satisfaction, and Pediatric Intensive Care.

Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Nursing Excellence and Quality.

Experience

Huntington Hospital Registered Nurse September 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months) Pasadena, California

Self-employed Registered Nurse June 2016 - June 2017 (1 year 1 month) Greater Los Angeles Area

Kaiser Permanente Registered Nurse January 2011 - June 2016 (5 years 6 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

Children's Hospital Los Angeles (CHLA)
Registered Nurse
September 1989 - January 2011 (21 years 5 months)
Greater Los Angeles Area

Sub Acute Saratoga Childrens Hospital Registered Nurse April 1988 - August 1989 (1 year 5 months) San Francisco Bay Area

Education

Martinez Memorial College

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1982 - 1986)